[
    {"question": "shall", "answer": "ska","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "has", "answer": "har","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "can", "answer": "kan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "must", "answer": "m책ste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "shall", "answer": "skall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "has", "answer": "har","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "is", "answer": "채r","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "was", "answer": "var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "becomes", "answer": "blir","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "became", "answer": "blev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "comes", "answer": "kommer","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "came", "answer": "kom","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "goes", "answer": "g책r","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "went", "answer": "gick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "gets", "answer": "f책r","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "got", "answer": "fick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "wants", "answer": "vill","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "wanted", "answer": "ville","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"}
]

